All right. And just to wrap up then, I
want to say again, this is a very
confusing time. Things are moving so
quickly. Do keep an eye on on the
documentation. I'm going to try and and
make sure that that I address things and
keep it up to date and look at the Q&A
and Udemy. I'll answer questions and and
always ask me try not to get distracted
by the noise. There's so much uh energy
over new announcements that turns out
not to be anything. Um, and so, uh,
yeah, just just don't don't let that
distract you. And recognize that the
models you use are no doubt going to be
even stronger than the ones I use
because new models come out every single
week. So, you will get different
results. You might get inconsistent
results and you might get better results
and you should take joy in that. And
please share them with me. I love to
hear about it. Put it on the Q&A. Share
the things that you discover. And
actually on that point, it's worth me
pointing out that that the projects that
we do together in this course, this is
very different to all the other courses
I've made in that there's not going to
just be like one bit of code that you
run and you get one result that will
match me. Every project is going to be
very different for for you and for me.
We're going to get different answers and
it's like a sort of choose your own
adventure thing. You'll be able to have
a lot of flexibility in how you do this
and you might get very different
outcomes and that's both really
exciting. It means that you're going to
see something unique to you. It also
introduces some challenges because if it
doesn't work, then it's not going to be
easy for me to reproduce that. So, we
we're going to have to figure that out
as we go. But keep that in mind. This is
going to be very different to other
courses because we're all going to have
slightly different experiences. And
look, you got something else with this
package, something that came with this
this Udemy course. Uh whether you wanted
it or not, it's it's like it's like a
mandatory extra that comes with it. And
that that is me. I come with this and
and I I am here to help you. And as it
happens, I actually enjoy helping
people. So So you're doing me a favor if
you message me. So at any point you can
you can hit me up in the Q&A. You can
send me an email. I always reply. If I
don't, then maybe it got in my spam
folder or something. Send another email
and I'll definitely reply. But but do
that. Uh connect with me on LinkedIn. I
love being connected. Uh, and I love
interacting with people. So, take me up
on it. Do it. Ask me the questions. And
also, I I encourage people to post about
your learning experience and and what
you create on LinkedIn. It's a great way
to draw attention to to all of the
progress you're making and the expertise
that you're building. And if you tag me
on your LinkedIn post, then I'll come in
and I'll weigh in and I'll add some
comments. And that's a great way to
amplify your accomplishment and get get
more visibility to the ways in which
you're building your expertise. And with
that and with that, let me show you
again the three weeks to being an expert
agentic coder our curriculum. But now
that box on the bottom left, that week
one, day one box, the agentic coding
landscape that is filled in to represent
that you've accomplished day one. You've
now got a sense of the landscape, the
eight stages, the different tools,
whether you're an IDE or a terminal.
You've you've got some of the landscape
in mind. Tomorrow is when we're going to
cover the foundations. We'll talk about
agents, the agents.md file that that is
at the heart of all of this. We'll
discuss context overall. But with that,
let's celebrate the fact that you're
already 7% complete with this course. I
like to do these like percentage
completes as we go so you have that
sense of accomplishment. We're 7% of the
way through which of course means
there's 93% of the way left but it's
going to be a great 93% starting
tomorrow with the foundations. I'll see
you then.